<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="Textbook.xsl"?>
<!--
To change this license header, choose License Headers in Project Properties.
To change this template file, choose Tools | Templates
and open the template in the editor.
-->

<textbooks>
    <book>
        <title>Violent Python</title>
        <author>TJ O'connor</author>
        <ISBN> 1597499579</ISBN>
        <publisher>Syngress</publisher>
        <date>9/22/2012</date>
        <abstract>
            Violent Python shows you how to move from a theoretical 
            understanding of offensive computing concepts to a practical 
            implementation. Instead of relying on another attacker’s tools, this
            book will teach you to forge your own weapons using the Python 
            programming language. This book demonstrates how to write Python 
            scripts to automate large-scale network attacks, extract metadata, 
            and investigate forensic artifacts. It also shows how to write code 
            to intercept and analyze network traffic using Python, craft and 
            spoof wireless frames to attack wireless and Bluetooth devices, 
            and how to data-mine popular social media websites and evade 
            modern anti-virus. 
        </abstract>
    </book>
    <book>
        <title>
            Black hat Python: Python Programming for hackers and
            pentesters
        </title>
        <author>Justin Seitz</author>
        <ISBN>1593275900</ISBN>
        <publisher>No Starch Press</publisher>
        <date>21/12/2014</date>
        <abstract>
            In Black Hat Python, the latest from Justin Seitz 
            (author of the best-selling Gray Hat Python), you’ll explore the 
            darker side of Python’s capabilities—writing network sniffers, 
            manipulating packets, infecting virtual machines, creating stealthy 
            trojans, and more.
        </abstract>
    </book>
    <book>
        <title>
            Kali Linux Revealed: Mastering the Penetration Testing 
            Distribution
        </title>
        <author>Raphael Hertzog</author>
        <ISBN>0997615605</ISBN>
        <publisher>Offsec Press</publisher>
        <date>06/05/2017</date>
        <abstract>
            In this book, we'll focus on the Kali Linux platform itself, and 
            help you understand and maximize Kali from the ground up. The 
            developers will walk you through Kali Linux features and 
            fundamentals, provide a crash course in basic Linux commands and 
            concepts, and then walk you through the most common Kali Linux 
            installation scenarios. You'll learn how to configure, troubleshoot 
            and secure Kali Linux and then dive into the powerful Debian package 
            manager. Throughout this expansive section, you'll learn how to 
            install and configure packages, how to update and upgrade your Kali 
            installation, and how to create your own custom packages. Then 
            you'll learn how to deploy your custom installation across 
            massive enterprise networks. Finally, you'll be guided through 
            advanced topics such as kernel compilation, custom ISO creation, 
            industrial-strength encryption, and even how to install crypto 
            kill switches to safeguard your sensitive information.
        </abstract>
    </book>
</textbooks>
