<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="Textbook.xsl"?> -->
<!--
To change this license header, choose License Headers in Project Properties.
To change this template file, choose Tools | Templates
and open the template in the editor.
-->

<textbook>
    <book>

        <title>Violent Python</title>
        <author>TJ O'connor</author>
        <info>
            <ISBN> 1597499579</ISBN>
            <publisher>Syngress</publisher>
            <date>9/22/2012</date>
            <abstract>
                Violent Python shows you how to move from a theoretical 
                understanding of offensive computing concepts to a practical 
                implementation. 
            </abstract>
            <category>IT</category>
            <state>N</state>
        </info>
    </book>
    <book>

        <title>
            Black hat Python: Python Programming for hackers and
            pentesters
        </title>
        <author>Justin Seitz</author>
        <info>
            <ISBN>1593275900</ISBN>
            <publisher>No Starch Press</publisher>
            <date>21/12/2014</date>
            <abstract>
                In Black Hat Python, the latest from Justin Seitz 
                (author of the best-selling Gray Hat Python), you’ll explore the 
                darker side of Python.
            </abstract>
            <category>IT</category>
            <state>N</state>
        </info>
    </book>
    <book>

        <title>
            Kali Linux Revealed: Mastering the Penetration Testing 
            Distribution
        </title>
        <author>Raphael Hertzog</author>
        <info>
            <ISBN>0997615605</ISBN>
            <publisher>Offsec Press</publisher>
            <date>06/05/2017</date>
            <abstract>
                In this book, we'll focus on the Kali Linux platform itself, and 
                help you understand and maximize Kali from the ground up.
            </abstract>
            <category>IT</category>
            <state>N</state>
        </info>
    </book>
    <book>

        <title>Fundamentals of economics</title>
        <author>William Boyes</author>
        <info>
            <ISBN>0538481196</ISBN>
            <publisher>Cengage Learning</publisher>
            <date>2011</date>
            <abstract>
                Based on the comprehensive two-semester text by the same 
                authors, this version of Economics boils down the formal economic 
                theories and concepts into their essential parts, emphasizing 
                domestic and international applications and policy issues. 
            </abstract>
            <category>Business</category>
            <state>N</state>
        </info>
    </book>
    
    <book>
        <title>Social Issues in Diagnosis </title>
        <author>Annemarie Goldstein Jutel, Kevin Dew</author>
        <info>
            <ISBN>9781421413006</ISBN>
            <publisher>John Hopkins University Press</publisher>
            <date>2014</date>
            <abstract>
                Diagnosis, the classification tool of medicine, serves an 
                important social role. It confers social status on those who 
                diagnose, and it impacts the social status of those diagnosed. 
                Studying diagnosis from a sociological perspective offers 
                clinicians and students a rich and sometimes provocative view 
                of medicine and the cultures in which it is practiced. Social 
                Issues in Diagnosis describes how diagnostic labels and the 
                process of diagnosis are anchored in groups and structures as 
                much as they are in the interactions between patient and doctor.
            </abstract>
            <category>Medical</category>
            <state>Sold</state>
        </info>
    </book>
</textbook>
